ballislife.com 2019-05-15

# Privacy Policy - Ballislife.com - Ballislife.com

Last updated: (5/24/2018)  
Ballislife LLC (“us”, “we”, or “our”) operates http://www.ballislife.com (the “Site”). This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information we receive from users of the Site.

This Privacy Policy only applies to BallIsLife Services and not to the practices of companies that BallIsLife does not own or control, including operators of Web sites that Users may visit before, during, or after visiting the Site, and the owners or publishers of the documents, advertisements, or postings and other products (collectively, the “Publications”) Users download, review, or otherwise access.

We use your information only for improving the Site. By using the Site, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy.

### Information Collection And Use

While using Site services, we may ask you for certain information that can be used to contact or identify you. This information may include, but is not limited to your name (“Personal Information”) and email address.

### Log Data

Like many site operators, we collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our Site (“Log Data”). This Log Data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type, browser version, the pages of our Site that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages and other statistics. In addition, we may use third party services such as Google Analytics that collect, monitor and analyze user data.

We may use your Personal Information to contact you with newsletters, marketing or promotional materials.

### Cookies

Cookies are files with small amount of data, which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a web site and stored on your computer’s hard drive. Like many sites, we use “cookies” to collect information. You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Site. [Your Cookie Consent](http://ballislife.com/cookie-consent/)

### Security

The security of your Personal Information is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about the security of the BallIsLife.com Web site, or need to contact us if you suspect a security breach, please e-mail us at info@ballislife.com.

### Changes To This Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy is effective as of (1/1/2005) and will remain in effect except with respect to any changes in its provisions in the future, which will be in effect immediately after being posted on this page. We reserve the right to update or change our Privacy Policy at any time and you should check this Privacy Policy periodically. Your continued use of the Service after we post any modifications to the Privacy Policy on this page will constitute your acknowledgment of the modifications and your consent to abide and be bound by the modified Privacy Policy. If we make any material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you either through the email address you have provided us, or by placing a prominent notice on our website.

### Contact Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us.
